A Guide to the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) records FA084
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC Microforms, J; 135 Reels
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Directors (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-06-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Finance (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-07-(01-07))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Finance-Banque De Paris (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-07-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Finance-Royalties (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-07-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Incorporation (Box 2, Card 849-08)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Legal (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Legal-Agrolimen S. A. (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-11)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Legal-Technical Service Agreement (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Reports (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-20)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: France S. A.: Staff (Reel J-69, Box 2, Card 849-22)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: G. M. B. H. Austria: Directors (Reel J-55, Box 1, Card 850-06-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: G. M. B. H. Austria: Finance (Reel J-55, Box 1, Card 850-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: G. M. B. H. Austria: Finance (Box 1, Card 850-07-(01-07))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: G. M. B. H. Austria: Legal (Reel J-55, Box 1, Card 850-11)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: G. M. B. H. Austria: Publicity (Reel J-55, Box 1, Card 850-19)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Capitalization (Reel J-66A, Box 2, Card 960-02-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Capital Stock-Shareholders (Reel J-66A, Box 2, Card 960-02-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Capital Stock-Prospectus (Reel J-66A, Box 2, Card 960-02)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-06-(01-08))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-66A, Box 2, Card 960-07-(01-21))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance-Investments Guarantees (Reel J-66A, Box 2, Card 960-07-(01-08))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance-Investments Guarantees (Reel J-66B, Card 960-07-(01-08))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance-Loans-American Express (Box 2, Card 960-07-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance-Loans-Cooley Loan (AID) (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-07-(01-06))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Finance-Projections (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-07-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Incorporation (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-08-(01-08))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Legal-Technical-Assistance Agreement (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Office (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Property-Raw Materials (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-17-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Publicity (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-19)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Reports (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-20-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: India Ltd.: Reports-Annual (Reel J-66B, Box 2, Card 960-20-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Staff (Box 2, Card 960-22-(01-05))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ireland Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 854-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ireland Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 854-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ireland Ltd.: Finance-Royalties (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 854-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ireland Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 854-11)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-07-(01-09))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-11-(01-09))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Legal-Formation Agreement (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Office (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Planning-Expansion (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-14)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Japan Ltd.: Report-Feasibility (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 993-20-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Jordan Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-64, Box 1, Card 995-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Directors (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Finance (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-07-(01-14))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Incorporation (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-08)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Legal (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Legal-Technical Service Agreement (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Middle East S. A. L. Lebanon (AAME): Office (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 990-12-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: N.V. The Netherlands Holland: Finance (Reel J-60, Box 2, Card 855-07-(01-05))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: N.V. The Netherlands Holland: Incorporation (Reel J-60, Box 2, Card 855-08-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: N.V. The Netherlands Holland: Legal (Reel J-60, Box 2, Card 855-11-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: N.V. The Netherlands Holland: Public Relations (Reel J-60, Box 2, Card 855-18)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: N.V. The Netherlands Holland: Staff (Reel J-60, Box 2, Card 855-22)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ontario Ltd. Canada: Directors (Reel J-50, Box 1, Card 880-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ontario Ltd. Canada: Finance (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 880-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ontario Ltd. Canada: Legal (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 880-11-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Ontario Ltd. Canada: Publicity (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 880-19)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-10))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-A.I.D. Guarantees (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-Loans-American Express Company (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-Loans-AOFC-Corn Agreement (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-Loans-AOFC-Corn Reports (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-Loans-Cooley (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Finance-Loans-Cooley-Agreement (Reel J-70, Box 1, Card 865-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Incorporation (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 865-08-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 865-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Legal-Technical Service Agreement (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 865-11)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Pakistan Ltd.: Office (Reel J-71, Box 1, Card 865-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Directors (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Finance (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-07-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Finance-A. I. D. Guarantees (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Finance-Loans-Cooley (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-07-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Legal (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Office (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Philippines Co. Inc.: Publicity (Reel J-76, Box 1, Card 866-19)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: (PVT) Ltd. Rhodesia: Directors (Reel J-77, Box 1, Card 965-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: (PVT) Ltd. Rhodesia: Finance (Reel J-77, Box 1, Card 965-07-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: (PVT) Ltd. Rhodesia: Legal (Reel J-77, Box 1, Card 965-11-(01-05))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: (PVT) Ltd. Rhodesia: Legal-Technical Assistance Agreement (Reel J-77, Box 1, Card 965-11-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: (PVT) Ltd. Rhodesia: Office (Reel J-77, Box 1, Card 965-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Quebec Ltd. Canada: Directors (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 881-06)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Quebec Ltd. Canada: Finance (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 881-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Quebec Ltd. Canada: Incorporation (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 881-08)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Quebec Ltd. Canada: Legal (Reel J-60, Box 1, Card 881-11-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Directors (Box 1, Card 0961-06-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Finance (Box 1, Card 0961-07-(01-07))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Finance-A.I.D. Guarantees (Box 1, Card 0961-07-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Legal (Box 1, Card 0961-11-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Planning-Expansion (Box 1, Card 0961-14-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Publicity (Box 1, Card 0961-19-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Reports-Feasibility (Box 1, Card 0961-20-(01-02))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: Thailand Co. Ltd.: Staff (Box 1, Card 0961-22-01)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Credit (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-05)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-06-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-07-(01-09))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Finance-Buxted Merger (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Finance-Royalties (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-07)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Incorporation (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-08)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-11-(01-04))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Legal-Allied Farm Foods Incorporated (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-11-(01-03))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Legal-Technical Service Agreement (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-11-(01-06))
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Legal-Technical Service Agreement-H. Macguinness (Dundalk Hatchery) (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-11)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Office (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-12)
  - AA (Arbor Acres) Farm: United Kingdom (UK) Ltd.: Reports (Reel J-80, Box 1, Card 852-20-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Credit (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-05)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Directors (Reel J-79, Box 1, Card 802-06)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07-(01-17))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Acquisition (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07-(01-11))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Acquisition-Closing Papers (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07-(01-07))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Acquisition-IRS (Internal Revenue Service) Ruling (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Disbursements (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Liquidation (Reel J-78, Box 1, Card 802-07-(01-08))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Finance-Loans-Ralston Purina-Line of Credit (Box 1, Card 802-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Insurance (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 802-09-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Legal (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Legal (Box 2, Card 802-11-(01-04))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Legal-International Genetics (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Legal-Stone's Poultry Farm (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Office (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-12-(01-05))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Office Procedure-Purchasing (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-12)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Organization (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-13)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Organization-History (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-13-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut: Reports (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-20-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Finance (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-07-(01-08))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Legal (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Legal-Purchase Agreements (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Legal-Tepper Negotiations (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Legal-Tepper Stocks (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Connecticut (Europe): Staff (Reel J-79, Box 2, Card 802-22-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Agency-Greece (Reel J-92, Box 2, Card 801-01-(01-06))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Directors (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-06-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Incorporation (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-08)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Insurance (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-09)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Finance (Reel J-77, Box 3, Card 801-07-(01-29))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Finance-Agreements (Reel J-77, Box 3, Card 801-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Finance-Associated Manufacturers International S. A. (Reel J-77, Box 3, Card 801-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Finance-Disbursements (Reel J-77, Box 2, Card 801-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Finance-Hartford National Bank & Trust Company (Reel J-77, Box 2, Card 801-07)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal (Reel J-77, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-07))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal (Reel J-78)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Aglio, Michael (Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Allen, R. W. (Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Assumption Agreement (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Patents (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Power of Attorney (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Qualifications (Reel J-78, Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-07))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Lists (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Africa (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Argentina (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Australia (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Austria (Reel J-55, Box 2, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Bahrain (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Belgium (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Bolivia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Brazil (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Bulgaria (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Canada (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-05))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Central America (Reel J-55, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Chile (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-China (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Columbia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Costa Rica (Reel J-55, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Denmark (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Dominican Republic (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Ecuador (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Egypt (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-El Salvador (Reel J-55, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Far East (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Fiji Islands (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-France (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Germany-East (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Germany-West (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Greece (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Guatemala (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Honduras (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Hong Kong (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Hungary (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-India (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Indonesia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Iran (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Iraq (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Ireland (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-04))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Israel (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Italy (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Japan (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-06))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Jordan (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Korea (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Kumait (Kuwait) (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Lebanon (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Luxembourg (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Malaysia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Mexico (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Netherlands (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-New Zealand (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Nicaragua (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Nigeria (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Pakistan (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Panama (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Paraguay (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Peru (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Philippines (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Portugal & Mozambique (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Rhodesia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Russia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Saudi Arabia (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Singapore (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Spain (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Spain (Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Sweden (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Switzerland (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Syria (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Taiwan (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Thailand (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Turkey (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-United Kingdom (Reel J-56, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-07))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-United Kingdom (Reel J-57)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-United States (Reel J-57, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Uruguay (Reel J-57, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Venezuela (Reel J-57, Box 3, Card 801-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Legal-Trademarks-Zambia (Reel J-57, Box 3, Card 801-11)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Office (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-12-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Organization (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-13)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Planning-Expansion-Denmark (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-14)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Planning-Expansion-Norway (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-14)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Planning-Expansion-Sweden (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-14)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Planning-Expansion (Reel J-78, Box 3, Card 801-14-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Publicity (Reel J-79, Box 3, Card 801-19-(01-12))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Publicity (Reel J-80)
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Publicity-AA Review (Box 3, Card 801-19-(01-09))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Publicity-Chik Chat (Box 3, Card 801-19-(01-07))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Research & Development (R & D) (Reel J-79, Box 3, Card 801-21-(01-02))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Research & Development (R & D)-Market Research (Reel J-79, Box 3, Folder 801-21-(01-03))
  - AA Farm Inc.: Delaware: Staff Meetings (Reel J-79, Box 3, Card 801-22-(01-05))
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Directors (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-06)
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Finance (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-07-(01-11))
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Finance-Royalties (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-07)
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Legal (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Publicity (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-19)
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Reports (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-20)
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Staff (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-22-(01-02))
  - AA Farm S. P. A.: Italy: Stockholders (Reel J-61, Box 3, Card 851-23)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Directors (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-06)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Finance (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-07-(01-10))
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Incorporation (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-08)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Legal (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-11)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Organization (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-13)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Publicity (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-19)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Reports (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-20)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Reports-Feasibility-Integrated Poultry (Box 1, Card 0832-20-(01-04))
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Brazil: Staff (Reel J-57, Box 1, Card 832-22)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Directors (Reel J-80, Box 3, Card 846-06)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Finance (Box 3, Card 846-07-(01-12))
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Finance-Agreements (Reel J-80, Box 3, Card 846-07-(01-02))
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Incorporation (Reel J-80, Box 3, Card 846-08)
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Legal (Reel J-80, Box 3, Card 846-11-(01-02))
  - AA Farm S. A. Avicultura: Switz (Switzerland): Stockholders (Reel J-80, Box 3, Card 846-23)
  - ABC (Agricola Brazil Central): Brazil: Finance (Reel J-12, Box 1, Card 327-07)
  - ACASA: El Salvador: Credit (Reel J-110, Box 1, Card 314-05)